(Sheldon:)This is a live shot of Kripke's lab
via a mini webcam I was able to install...
(Sheldon:)...thanks to a dollar bill discreetly placed
in the night janitor's shirt pocket.
(Sheldon:)At the same time, I also secured
large quantities of these chemicals...
(Sheldon:)...above the tiles in the drop ceiling.
(Raj:)Sheldon, you remind me
of a young Lex Luthor.
(Sheldon:)You flatter me, sir.
(Leonard:)-Let me guess, motion sensors?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)The reaction will be triggered when
Kripke reaches the center of the room.
Mwa, ha, ha.
(Leonard:)I gotta say, I am really impressed.
(Leonard:)This is truly the Sheldon Cooper way
to get even.
[FARTING SOUND]
(Sheldon:)It may be low-tech...
(Sheldon:)...but I still maintain
the whoopee cushion has comic validity.
(Raj:)Here comes Kripke.
LEONARD:
Who's that with him?
RAJESH: I believe that's the president
of the university.
(Leonard:)-The board of directors. Abort! Abort!
-There is no abort.